# JAN CZIZIKOW



# PERSONAL DETAILS

- **□** 12 June 1992
- · +(86) 131-6700-7112
- □ jan\_czizikow@hotmail.com
- www.janczizikow.com

# **PROFILE**

Currently a senior undergraduate business student in Donghua University, living in China since 2012. Passionate about marketing, PR, branding and serious about future career in related business field. Highly motivated, proactive and adaptable fast-learner, eager to further develop his skills through a challenging experience. I believe that education is based on two pillars: theory and practice, thus, I engaged in a couple of part-time positions through studies.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Social Cloud China

Full & Part-time / 1 year July 2015 - May 2016

## Winwho Technology

Part-time / 4 months March 2015 - June 2015

#### Fujian Hotel

Full-time / 2 months July 2014 - 2014 August

## Marketing Assistant

- Assisted in developing marketing campaigns
- Assisted in organizing events and press conferences
- Created and maintained relationships and partnerships with media and sponsors
- Organized and attended meetings with clients and potential partners
- Compiled reports and marketing materials (newsletters, social media content, press releases, brochures, posters)

## Event Marketing Intern

- Assisted in planning, organizing and implementation of online and offline events
- Product and brand promotion via public relation activities
- Edited, maitaned and updated "财神所聘 / Caishen Locksreen" app wallpapers

## Hotel Guest Relation Officer

- Offered assistance and provided needed or sought information to the guests
- Solicited guest responses, concerning their satisfaction and complaints
- Conducted inspections of the lobby, monitored officers, reported unusual occurrences, handled lost-and-found matters

# **EDUCATION**

## Donghua University, China

2014 - Present

# Beijing Language and Culture University, China

2012 - 2014

## Bachelor of Business Administration

- GPA 3.2/ 4.0
- English-taught Business degree with Chinese courses

# Chinese Language Studies

- Mastered 2,500 commonly used words and related grammar patterns
- Passed HSK5 with a total score of 235/300 06.2014

# SKILLS & EXPERTISE

## Languages

Polish: Native Russian: Bilingual English: Fluent

Chinese (Mandarin): Proficient

## Knowledge

Social Media Marketing Marketing Communications Public Relations

#### **Technical**

Microsoft Office: Advanced HTML5 & CSS3: Intermediate Adobe Photoshop: Basic Adobe Illustrator: Basic

## Interests

Traveling Skateboarding Digital Marketing & Web Design

# **REFEREES**

#### Ambra Schillirò

Director of Social Cloud
□ +(86) 158-2112-2831
□ ambra.schilliro@socialcloudchina.com

# Marko Ljubičič

Professor at Donghua University

□ (+86) 150-2124-2364

□ mr.ljubicic@gmail.com